free-spider-solitaire.com 2019-12-01

# TreeCardGames Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

At TreeCardGames, the privacy of our users and visitors is of extreme importance to us. TreeCardGames is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.

**What information do we collect?**

We don't collect any personally identifiable information about you. You are not required to provide personally-identifying information to use our Online Games.

**Cookies**

Our Online Games uses cookies to keep track of users online preferences and game statistics. Also some of our third party links and advertisers use cookies.

Ads appearing in any of our Free Online Games are provided by Google. They are used in the following way:

\- Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website.

\- Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

\- Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

\- For [more information](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) about Google's uses of data/information.

**Your Consent**

By using our Online Games, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the following link: [www.treecardgames.com/support.htm](https://www.treecardgames.com/support.htm)

This document was last updated on May 10, 2018.
